ticketsmarche.com 2013-06-01

# Ticketsmarche.com - Tickets for Concerts, Sports, Art, Theater, Family, Cinema, Sight Seeing

Welcome to Ticketsmarche! Please know that it is very important to us to protect your personal information. You must also know that we totally respect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy below is there to explain how we handle the information you share with us. The policy applies to everyone who uses our services, including call center, website, or walk-in customers. The policy also applies to every piece of information provided to us by you.   
By using our services, you are accepting the terms and conditions we describe here:

 ** _Consumer Privacy at Ticketsmarche  
_**  
At Ticketsmarche, we respect our user's privacy and we understand the importance of the information they share with us. The below text shows the basic information policies and practices we use on this site.

 ** _Information we may collect_**

We may collect personal information that we can identify you with, such as your name, and other contact details when you log on to our site, or when provided by our business partners, and/or from third parties. 

We may also collect other information in the following ways:

\- Our server logs automatically information such as your browser type, language, your time of visit, your IP address. This information helps us track movements around our site and helps us understand customer trends.

\- We may provide your computer with cookies which help you personalize your experience on our site

We assume that all of our users are above the age of 13. We therefore do not knowingly collect information from children under that age and we fully comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

 ** _Information others may collect_**

\- Third party companies and/or advertisement networks may advertise on our website.

\- We do not provide them with any personal information 

\- These advertisers may use tools such as tracking cookies to collect information about your computers when you interact with their advertisements.

\- If you post information on our site about yourself or others through our site, we can not control who reads your blogs or posts or what they may do with     such information. You are therefore advised to use caution when doing so.

 _ **How we may use information we collect**     
_  
We may use information to: 

\- Fulfill your requests for our services and products. 

\- Suggest products and services that may interest you 

\- Customize advertisements and website content that you see

\- Help use of our site

\- Help us improve the usage of our site, services, and products

\- Identify our users and help protect from falsified transactions and wrong use of our site, and

\- Enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.ticketsmarche.com/showNews.html?idNews=148).

 ** _With whom we may share information we collect_**

We will never share your personal information except as explained below, or except after we get your authorization. We may share this information with:

\- Event organizers, such as the venues, the promoters, artists, and fan clubs ,teams, leagues, or any other entities specialized in bringing events to our country

\- Ticketsmarche owned or affiliated businesses

\- Service providers who are performing services on our behalf, such as the couriers and credit card companies

\- Our partners which we carefully select to offer you their services and promotions on our site or offline, and

\- Other third parties when we have to such as legal requirements or helping to protect the safety of other users.

\- Other information that is not considered as personal may be shared with advertisers and others.

 ** _Security_**

We try our best and take physical and electronic measures to help protect our users information from unauthorized access or disclosure.

 ** _Changes to our Privacy Policy_**

Our privacy Policy may be updated occasionally to reflect changes in our services and business operations. If serious changes are done to the policy, you will be notified by email to the email address you most recently used in accessing our site.

 _ **How to contact us**  
_  
If you have any questions about this summary, our Privacy Policy, or our information practices, please contact us by email or postal mail below:

Ticketsmarche  
127 Merghany St,   
Heliopolis, 11341  
Cairo, Egypt  
legal@ticketsmarche.com

© Ticketsmarche. All rights reserved.
